Do I understand correctly that Rus' and the
я правильно понимаю что Русь и
Russian Empire are one and the same Well,
Российская империя - это одно и то же Ну
initially there was Rus' Yes, then it became the
изначально была Русь Да потом стала
Russian Empire, then the
Российская империи потом потом
Russian Empire, then the Soviet Union, then it
Российская империя потом Советский Союз
turns out that Rus' is the same as the
то получается Русь - Это то же самое что
Soviet
Советский
Union
Союз
M You have led me into a dead end, of course it is
М Ты меня в тупик завёл конечно
interesting, very
интересно очень даже
interesting, Rus', the Soviet Union
интересно Руси Советский Союз
Well done, you can do it Yes, yes,
Молодец умеешь Да
hello, you are
да здравствуйте вы
LDPR Hello, I recently met
ЛДПР Здравствуйте я встречал уже недавно
one LDPR [ __ ] from Samara, she is originally from
одну ЛДПР суу из Самары родом Она сейчас
Moscow now And
в Москве А вы
how did I know you from this, we
откуда я узнал ты с этого мы же с тобой
talked with you from
говорили с
Altai Hello,
Алтая Привет
dear, guardian angel to you, Christmas trees I
родной ангела тебе хранителя ёлки Я тебя
recognized you, it was just a divine meeting You
узнал это просто божественная встреча Ты
were then just in some kind of shirt Or
тогда была просто в какой-то рубашке Или
there or in a T-shirt and were drinking And now you are
там или в футболке и бухала А теперь ты
LDPR tsa but the flag is the same no, no,
ЛДПР ца но флаг тот же самый нет нет
why did I just come out of my soul my
почему просто я из души вышла у меня
mother-in-law is in the LDPR, she
свекровь в это в ЛДПР состоит она мне
brought me a T-shirt I just put it on
футболку принесла я её просто
I am an imperialist
одела я имперец
imperialist
имперец
ldc Well, by the way, Zhirinovsky also
лдц Ну кстати Жириновский тоже за россие
supported Russia, for the
топил за
Empire, for Rus', so for Rus' or for
Империю за Русь так за Русь или за
Empire Well, let's start with the fact that the
Империю Ну давай начнём с того что
Russian Empire and Rus' are well, the
Российская империя и Русь - это ну
Russian
Российская
Empire, Russia is practically the same thing,
империя Россия это тически одно и тоже
and the Soviet Union, oh
и Советский Союз
wait Well, if my T-shirt bothers you,
од подожди Ну если тебя смущает моя
I can change from M
футболка я могу переодеться М В
to another With what
какую в другую С какой
inscription do you want to look at,
надписью хочешь посмотреть
come on, look, come on, there will be options now The
давай смотри давай варианты сейчас будет
main thing is that without a T-shirt it doesn't come out
Главное чтобы без футболки на вылезло
Altai Novo-Altai Vodokanal, damn, not in the
Алтай Ново Алтайской водоканал блин не в
LDPR, it would be cool, come on, Bring back the LDPR,
ЛДПР было прикольно давай Верни ЛДПР ну
really Well, what's the difference Anyway, you ca
реально Ну какая разница Всё равно тебя
n't be seen, no, you have a T-shirt, you need an
не видно нет тебе футболка ж тебе
inscription, or just chat Well, both are just that
надпись или просто пообщаться Ну и то и
when I talked to the LDPR, I considered it more
то просто вот когда с ЛДПР счита
interesting than to the Vodokanal, Bring back, Bring back LGBT Let's talk about that, let's talk about what kind of LGBT, LDPR, what kind of LGBT,
интересней общался чем с водоканальная
I say LDPR,
давай какой ЛГБТ ЛДПР какой ЛГБТ говорю
Bring back and let's talk No, let's talk like this
ЛДПР Верни и поговорим
with you Yes, let's talk
давай Нет давай так поговорим с тобой Да
with the LDPR, sorry No, let's do it like this, okay,
давай с ЛДПР поговорим жал Нет давай так
okay, let's look, do I
ладно лад давай смотри я правильно
understand correctly that Rus' and the Russian Empire are the
понимаю что Русь и Российская империя -
same Well, initially  there was Rus
это одно и то же Ну изначально была Русь
Yes then it became the Russian Empire then then the
Да потом стала Российской империей потом
Russian Empire then the Soviet
потом Российская империя потом Советский
Union then it turns out Rus - It's the
Союз то получается Русь - Это то же
same as the Soviet
самое что Советский
Union
Союз
[music]
[музыка]
M You've got me into a dead end of course it's
М Ты меня в тупик завёл конечно
interesting very
интересно очень даже
interesting Rus Soviet
интересно Руси Советский
Union Well done you can do it yes yes handsome Come on think think you can you can Well
Союз Молодец умеешь да да красавчик
you yourself
думай можешь можешь можешь Ну ты же сам
understand perfectly well
прекрасно понимает
that no that is ru Rus - it's Rus so it
что нет то есть ру Русь - это Русь так
turns out there is no connection between Rus and the Soviet
то получается между Русью и советским
Union
союзом нету
Well as I told you Why is there no
связи Ну как тебе сказано Почему нет
connection It's all historically little by little
связи Это же всё исторически потихонечку
it all moved
это всё двигалось
moved the Soviet Union is the same as the
двигалось Советский Союз - это то же что
Russian Empire so now
и Российская империя так вот теперь
tell me honestly are
скажи мне честно
you writing it all down Yes
ты это всё записываешь Да
[music]
[музыка]
honestly Well I don't like it when they
честно Ну вот не нравится мне когда
write it down Well come on Well it's just interesting
записывают Ну давай Ну просто интересно
I love communication this
Я люблю общение это
communication Well no well I won't
общение Ну нет ну не буду я ничего
say anything first of all what Honestly I
говорить вопервых че Честно с тобой
even told you Maybe it's
сказал даже Моть
good because whatever I
есть хороо потому что то чтобы я не
say you'll post it all later not the
сказала ты это всё потом выложишь уже не
first
первый
time the second time I
раз второй я это
met this Well done Well I won't say
встретила Молодец Ну я говорить не буду
first of all That is to say you
вопервых То есть ты
recognize your Guardian Angel  That is, you
призна ангела вам Хранители То есть ты
say that Rus' has nothing to do with the
шь Что Русь не имеет отношения к
Soviet Union and with Russia, I tell you,
Советскому Союзу и к России я тебе
may God protect you, may God bless you,
храните Дай Бог вам всего
Altai, chatter, LDPR, water
хорошего Алтай болтай ЛДПР
utility. Well, about you, I say water utility. Come on,
водоканал Ну по вас я говорю водоканал
my dear, come on, all the
Да ну давай мой хороший давай всего
best, look, eh,
хорошего посмотри э
Russia has broken loose, LDPR,
Росси сорвалась ЛДПР
damn, comment, like, Pete, pska,
блин комент лайк Пит пска здравствуйте
hello, hello, we seemed to have
здравствуйте мы с вами вроде когда-то
communicated with you once, it seemed like you had a mush
общались у вас вроде Муш ная сло было
or not, God forbid, I confused you with someone.
или нет не что не дай Бог с кем-то
Where are you from? Well, Russia. Well, I can see from your face
откуда Ну Россия Ну я вижу по лицу город
what kind of city Arkhangelsk is
какой Архангельск
Ponya. And you had some kind of rallies in the
Поня А это у вас там какие-то митинги в
villages there, that there were no roads or medicine, not
сёлах были что ни дороги ни медицины не
two or three years ago, not that, in the
было года два-три назад не это вот в
Arkhangelsk region today I read that
Архангельской области сегодня читал что
there. And do you live in Arkhangelsk itself or
там А вы именно в самом Архангельске или
somewhere in the region, no, not in Arkhangelsk.
где-то в области живёте нет в
And what? And what? My grandmother
Архангельске А что А что у меня бабушка
is from Arkhangelsk. Oh, great, where
родом из Архангельска О классно откуда
exactly is she from? How is she from? My great-
именно Ну как она получается Они
grandmother and grandfather were from Ukraine when the
прабабушка с дедом из Украины когда
Bolsheviks came.  exiled to
пришли большевики их сослали в
Arkhangelsk like Kurku grandma was born there
Архангельск как Курку там родилась
then they sang from there back to
бабушка потом они оттуда спели назад в
Ukraine Oh wow they even celebrated in Arkhangelsk
Украину О нифига в архангельско
yeah Cool And did you come to
да Круть А вы что сами приехали в
Arkhangelsk yourself well I was born Unfortunately
Архангельск ну я родилась К сожалению
here come on that is your parents clearly didn't
тут ну же то есть Ваши родители явно не
come here of their own free will
по своей воле сюда туда заехали
True Well no they are also like natives but
Правда Ну нет они типа тоже коренные но
grandma and grandpa are there yeah yeah that is I
бабушка с дедушкой там да да то есть я
can't imagine a person who let's say in a
не представляю человека который скажем в
sober mind would voluntarily go to
трезвом уме добровольно поедет в
Arkhangelsk to live Lomonosov and then he ran away from there
Архангельск жить Ломоносов и то оттуда
true And your great-grandmother and great-grandfather
правда А ваши прабабушка и прадедушка
Where are they from oh
Откуда
by the way one was from Belarus the
родом ой один кстати из Беларуси был
second one was there I don't know the second one there history
второй там Второй не знаю там история
is silent
умалчивает
that is they were sent like that Yes they were exiled there yes it
то есть их так и послали Да сослали туда
turns out Well one survived the second one
да получается Ну один выжил второй
no I understood And what are the delights of life in
нет понял А какие прелести жизни в
Arkhangelsk can you
Архангельске можете
name are you kidding
назвать вы издеваетесь
Well you are kidding
Ну вы издеваетесь
well Can I ask a question Are you from
хорошо Можно вопрос на вопрос Вы из
Russia
России
no from Estonia I have an Estonian flag on my
нет из Эстонии У меня же флаг Эстонии
back I hope you are not writing it down for me No
сзади Я надеюсь вы мне не записываете Да
what are you saying no Well just What
что нет Ну просто Какие можно
delights can there be are you kidding
прелести вы издеваетесь
Well in  each in each territory there is
Ну в каждо в каждой территории есть
something that is better to live in Arkhangelsk than
что-то чем в Архангельске лучше жить чем
in Europe for example you know we have the
в Европе например вот знаете у нас
only plus in our Arkhangelsk
Единственный плюс у нас в Архангельской
region and the residence of Father Frost
области а резиденция Деда Мороза
All I do not believe that Father Frost is so
Всё я не верю что Дед Мороз настолько
crazy as to go and make a
сумасшедший чтобы поехать и делать
residence for himself in the Arkhangelsk
резиденцию себе в архангельскую
region
область
well in fact there is google if you do not
ну по факту есть погуглить если не
believe the Great Mouth
верите Великий уст
lives
живёт
listen to the question Yes here is still an
слушайте вопрос Да вот вс-таки
interesting question How is it that the
вопрос интересный Как так получается что
Arkhangelsk region is the richest region there is
Архангельская область богатейший регион
access to the sea fish resources There are forests
есть выход к морю рыбный ресурсы Там лес
minerals But they live poorly in
полезные ископаемые А живут бедно в
barracks I am asked by a person
бараках меня спрашивает человека
who I also ask myself this
который я тоже задаю себе этим
question so I can not answer you
вопросом поэтому я не могу Вам ответить
Why I do not know You see when I
Почему я не знаю Понимаете когда я
come to buy fish I always scream
прихожу покупать рыбу Я всегда ору
And we do not live by the sea it feels like
А мы что живём не на море такое ощущение
our fish is caught there in the
что наши рыбу вылавливают там в
Mediterranean Sea with gold chains
Средиземном море золотыми цепями потому
because it costs so much and how much does
что она столько стоит вот а сколько
fish cost in your place Damn well approximately I dont know
рыба Блин ну примерно я же не знаю
how much well damn 500 rubles is easy Well
сколько ну блин рубле 500 это спокойно
oh Let me not tell you  lie
Ну ой Давайте я вам не буду врать
I well, as if you understand, it's 5 dollars per
я ну как бы понимаете это 5 долларов за
kilogram
килограмм
It's not You see, in dollars,
Это нет Понимаете в долларах то у нас
we don't have it, I don't even buy cod now No,
нет я сейчас даже треску и не покупаю Не
500 rubles is 5 dollars, it's something
ну 500 руб - это 5 долларов это что-то
per kilogram You know what I want to
за килограмм Это я вам знаете что хочу
tell you When I was little We
сказать Когда я была маленькая Мы
bought haddock for the cat, it was the
покупали пикшу для кошки это были
nineties, believe it or not And even in the
девяностые года вот верите нет И даже в
nineties We bought haddock for the cat
девяностые Мы покупали пикшу для кошки
Now I'm living in 20D, fifth Damn, I eat this haddock
сейчас я живу 20Д пятый Блин я эту пикшу
myself
жру сама
And you ask me How much does
и А Вы меня спрашиваете Сколько стоит
risk cost, that's all And how much does peak cost now, too,
риска вот и всё А сколько пик сейчас
expensive Well,
тоже дорого Ну
how much do
сколько
we have, well, 300 rubles per kilogram,
ну у нас ну Рублей 300 за килограмм
easily 3 dollars per kilogram of
спокойно 3 доллара за килограмм
haddock 300 rubles of our Russians Well, yes, it is
пикша 300 рубле наших русских Ну да это
According to the international standard, 3 dollars per kilogram of
По международному 3 доллара за килограмм
haddock
пикши
Damn, and that's what you
Блин
catch there Yes,
да и это у вас там ловят ва Да вы же на
of course, you live by the sea And we live by the sea I
живёте конечно А мы живём в море мне
always want to ask
всегда хочется спросить вы там золотыми
Do you catch them with gold chains or
цепями что ли их
something Yeah, that's the word
капец Не то слово
and what do you even eat in the Arkhangelsk
а что вы вообще едите в Архангельской
region and what do you even think about the
области а что вы вообще думаете про
war well I think that so much money
войну ну я думаю что столько денег
as Russia threw into the war it was already
сколько Россия бросила на войну уже
possible to feed people in the Arkhangelsk region
можно было людей в Архангельской области
squid
кормить кальмарами
coconuts with personal
кокосами с личными
masseurs Well we are not used to squid
массажистами Ну кальмаро мы не привыкли
masseurs This is good
массажисты Это хорошо
of course Explain to me Why can all countries
конечно Объясните мне Почему все страны
tell Russia that it is not allowed to do this
и могут сказать России что так делать
everyone says Russia
нельзя все и говорят Россия так делать
cannot do this Russia like a drunk stump says I will beat
нельзя Россия как пьяный пни говорит я
everyone's faces in now And how do they
вам сейчас морды набью всем А как они
say They say We sanctions that your
говорят Они говорят Мы санкции что ваши
sanctions just understand that if
санкция просто понимаете что если
Crimea was allowed at the time it is
разрешили Крым в своё время это же
wrong accordingly another country
неправильно соответственно другая страна
can say I also eh you were mine
может при и сказать Я тоже э те была моя
right how old are you
правильно сколько вам лет
By the way can you Well you just didn't you just
Кстати а можно Ну вы просто не вы просто
said that about the nineties I also I was in
говорили что про девяностый Я тоже я
eighty-first I am interested
восемьдесят первого года мне интересно
yes Or did you still live in the Soviet Union
да Или вы Советский Союз ещё застали
eighty-second eighty-second oh you
восемьдесят второй восемьдесят второй о
see I am 43 you are 42 we are the same age Almost yes yes yes So So yes it
видите мне 43 вам 42 мы ровесники Почти
turns out that you
да да да Так Так что да то получается вы
lived a little bit more of the Soviet Union and the
застали ещё чуть-чуть Советского Союза и
nineties yes yes What are you of course my
девяностых да да Вы что конечно у меня
mother  there was a teacher and like that's all I by
мама была учителька и как бы весь так Я
the way remember the pasta that came
кстати макароны помню которые приходили
from Italy as humanitarian
из Италии как гуманитарная
aid humanitarian aid to Arkhangelsk
помощь гуманитарная помощь в Архангельск
from Italy pasta you definitely don't
из Италии макароны вы меня точно не
write me down definitely don't
записываете точно не
write me down I'm just the first time I hear I was
записывай я просто Впервые слышу
surprised about pasta it's not true
удивился про макароны не правда
humanitarian aid came And what's
приходила гуманитарная помощь А что
not coming now the
сейчас не
question of countries Maron was sent correctly not And in
вопрос Марон отправляли правильно не А в
this in Arkhangelsk now people somehow
этом в архангельски сейчас люди как-то
remember Well gratitude to the Italians
вспоминают Ну благодарность итальянцам
for the topic of the crown
за тема короны
humanitarian aid You know I'm probably the
гуманитарку Вы знаете я наверное
only person who remembers this
единственный человек который это
No well really everyone else forgets Yes well my
Не ну правда остальные всё забывают
mother was just a teacher it was
ну меня просто мама была учителька было
very bad And you are also a teacher or how did
очень плохо А вы тоже учителька или кем
you follow in your mother's footsteps not I studied
вы пошли по маминым стопам не я училась
but I realized that it's not my thing And what do you
но поняла что это не моё А кем
work in a
работаете в доме
nursing home uh looking after the
престарелых ээ присматривается за
elderly
престарелыми
Yes cult organizer I don't believe it that
Да культ организатор не поверить а то
is you do all sorts of entertainment for them
есть вы им всякие развлечения делаете
there dancing games there such Yes Evening Evening
там танцы игры там такое Да Вечор Вечор
yes
да
interesting yes That's also good Well how can I
интересно да Это тоже хорошо Ну как
say and of
сказать а муж
course there is a husband and two children How old are the
есть конечно и двое детей Сколько лет
children
детям
oh one is 17 the other is
ой тому 17 другому
15 children where do they want to go to study
15 дети куда хотят ехать учиться
Well one there is  cars I'm
Ну один там по автомобилям у меня
laughing Lash
угорает Лаш
who are you going where do you want to go to Arkhangelsk to
который ты куда хочет у в Архангельск в
Moscow what Moscow what
Москву какая Москва что
can you do Yes I don't know he didn't even think about it
мога Да не знаю он даже не думал про это
ty And it turns out you still live in Soviet
ти А живёте получается ещё в советских
houses yes
домах да
no we built our own house so
нет у нас свой дом построили
you interrogate me as if I'm
так вы меня как допрашивает как мне
interested just well look My
интересно просто ну смотрите У меня
grandmother grandmother yes was born there I'm
бабушка бабушка да родилась там мне
interested If she lived there I would have been
интересно Если б она жила там я бы
born there and I'm interested how people
родился там и мне интересно как люди
live because she
живут потому что она в детстве
told me about Arkhangelsk as a child she said that there were
рассказывала про архангель говорила что
still wooden houses then your
ещё были тогда деревянные дома вас
Grandmother was from Arkhangelsk Well I told you
Бабушка была с арханге Ну я же говорил
she was born there it turns out and No they
она родилась там получается и Нет они
No they they remained eh wooden houses
Нет они они остались э деревянные дома
someone even
кто-то даже там и
lives there And how do people live now in
живёт А как люди живут сейчас в
wooden
деревянных
houses well somehow they There they repair
домах ну как-то их Там ремонтируют
here and there And why can't the
туда-сюда А почему не могут им
state give them normal
государство дать нормальные
houses there is no money from the state to
дома денег нету государства чтобы
build but but new houses
строить но но новые дома
I wonder if by the way are you accidentally
Интересно а вы кстати случайно может вы
recording me because you
меня записываете потому что вы несколько
asked this several times I see you have two
раз это пере спросили Я вижу у вас двое
headphones like that are going you are
наушников таких идут вы меня
recording me I understand overdid it Hello Where are
записываете на понял переборщил Привет
you
Вы
from Russia Yes I can see by your face And
откуда Россия Да я вижу по лицу А город
what city is the city  Chita
какой город Чита
Zabaikalsky
Забайкальский
Krai
край
Yes Cool My father
Да Прикольно У меня отец там
served there He's ashamed of you now I
служил ему стыд за вас теперь В
mean Yes it
смысле
turns out some kind of like that he too when the
Да оказывается какойто так он тоже как
Soviet Union fell apart he moved to the
Советский Союз развалился он переехал в
USA moved me little
США меня маленького перевёз
Great power and the Soviet Union and
Великая держава а Советский Союз и
Russia are sad which can't really do anything
Россия унылая которая ничего реально не
in this life and you really you are
может в этой жизни и Вы реально вы
now using we gave the first sound it
сейчас пользуетесь мы подали пер звук
turns out we stole it Yes flew nanu
оказывается мы его украли Да летали нану
And why still no one flies to
А почему до сих пор не летает никто на
it never flew to runes anymore you are
неё не летал никогда в руны больше вы
nobody Yes but for some reason you use our our
никто Да но почему-то вы нашим нашим
internet you use Yes our
интернетом вы пользуетесь Да нашими
phones we all our CIA everything I
телефонами мы всё наше ЦРУ всё я
use my own internet
пользуюсь своим собственным интернетом
which I have at home for which I pay I don't
который у меня дома за который я плачу я
pay America So
не плачу Америке Так
American is the internet
что американский это интернет
all American Yes all this was
американский весь Да всё это китайцы
made by the Chinese All this Chinese equipment
сделали Всё это китайское оборудование
you didn't make so the internet itself
вы не сделали так сам интернет
American through the Pentagon everything goes through
американский через Пентагон всё проходит
everything Look all your sites see everything in the
всё Смотри все твои сайты видят всё в
White House you understand you can't do anything else
Белом доме понимаешь вы больше ничем
only the internet more
ться не можно только интернетом больше
why are you every Russian Yes on the
сдела почему Вы каждый русский Да на
phone the American operating
телефоне американская операционная
system either iOS or Android yes
система либо iOS либо Android да
American all your data is in
американская все ваши данные находятся в
our CIA everything  yes the first man in
нашем ЦРУ всё да первый человек в
space Russian Russian not Russian
космосе российский русский не российский
but Soviet Soviet it does not exist Soviet
а Советский Советский его нету советски
everything And we destroyed the Soviet Union Yes we
всё А мы развалили Советский Союз Да мы
won the Cold War and destroyed the
победили в холодной войне и уничтожили
Soviet Union we destroyed it looks like
Советский Союз мы развалили
today will be hot like subscribe
походу сегодня будет жар лайк подписка
to
ко
Hello now I can hear you super to
Здравствуйте вот теперь вас слышно супер
you heart where are you from We already
вам сердечко Вы откуда Мы же уже с вами
talked to you Well I didn't quite
разговаривали Ну я не совсем
remember it was just hard to hear
запомнил просто плохо было слышно
so we switched Where are you from Kursk
поэтому переключили Откуда вы из Курска
oh from Kursk now I'll remember I asked if they don't
о из Курска теперь вспомню Я спросил или
bomb you there Yes you said they bomb
там не бомбят вас Да вы сказали бомбят
I just the connection was really bad now you're
Я просто связь была вообще очень плохая
running in a bomb shelter super
бегаете
no it's
нет
hard
тяжело Для
Why Well basically you yourself how are
чего Ну в принципе та вы сами как что
you afraid of bombs Well that's not the point I
вам боятся бомбочек Ну Дело не в этом Я
just don't understand the point Well
просто не понимаю смысла Ну
yes you understand The point is that they bomb on
да понимаете Дело в том что бомбят по
certain As they say early section
определённым Как говорится раном участка
And you are in the area section that doesn't bomb the
А вы в районе участке который не бомбит
course itself Kursk also flies in and it's
самого курс по курску тоже прилетает и
not bad but thank God in my
неплохо но чу слава Богу в моём
area if something happens it gets
районе если что-то бывает то оно там же
knocked
сбивается
down there Yeah I got it and how do you  here in Kursk people
Угу Понял а как вы вот в Курске люди
feel about this war already want
относитесь к этой войне уже хотите чтобы
it to end faster Well let's start with the
она закончилась побыстрее Ну начнём с
fact that it seems to me that all people want
того что мне кажется все люди хотят
everything to end faster not only
чтобы всё побыстрее закончила не только
in Russia not only in Ukraine but in general
в России не только на Украине а вообще
everywhere the same as in these countries where
везде так само как и в нных странах где
military actions are taking place Well that is I
происходят боевые действия Ну то есть Я
understood that there is no longer this euphoria of
так понял что уже нету вот этой эйфории
sharpening that there we will reach Berlin And there was Well there was Yes there was
заточки что там дойдём до Берлина А было
in twenty-second something
Ну было Да было в двадцать втором что-то
like that Have you seen somewhere that people walked
такое Вы где-то видели чтобы люди ходили
with Well I don't know what with banners
с Ну я не знаю там чем с транспарантами
we will find up to Yes and they hung them on cars and there
найдём до на Да и на машины вешали и там
all sorts of yes yes no
всякие да да нет
field Damn I don't know you can you can
поле Вот блин я не знаю юкату можно
give free rein to your
можно давать волю своим
feelings would be ti too oh also it
чувствам бы ти
was like that And now look
было тому подобно Да и Теперь смотрите
now yes some here in the Kursk region
теперь да какие-то вот Курской области
yes
да
some yes well
какие-то да ну
therefore you know that you can't judge a nation by one person You know No well you
поэтому знаете что по одному человеку
can't judge a nation by one person
Нет ну по одному человеку нации не судит
the same as in Ukraine too come on
так само как и на Украине тоже есть
Dava come on let's
давай Дава давайте давайте давайте
simplify our conversation and I will ask you How are
упрости наш разговор и я спрошу вас Как
you  do you think who is to blame for the fact that Putin
вы считаете кто виноват в том что Путин
attacked Ukraine Putin attacked
напал на Украину Путин нападал на
Ukraine Yeah, I got it And what did he do?
Украину Ага понял А что он
What did he do? What did
Укра что сделал
Zelensky do to prevent
вос А что сделал Зеленский для того
this from
чтобы это не
happening? Zelensky didn't attack another
произошло Зеленский не нападал на другую
country Wait Zelensky promised that he would
страну Подождите Зеленский обещал что он
stop, stop,
прекратит прекратит ные
those actions don't stop. Look,
те не прекращается Да смотри Да
let's make it worse Why is it worse now?
давай е хуже Почему хуже теперь Да
Now the fighting has moved to the
теперь боевые действия перенесли в
Kursk region Yes, absolutely
курскую область Да абсолютно
right, he did it in those territories, it's worse in
вернон сдел те территориях е хуже так в
Kursk, look The point is that
Курской смотри Суть в том что задача
Zelensky's task is to make it so bad, it's worse in the
Зеленского так сделать плохо хуже в
Kursk region, Belgorod, Bryansk, and then
Курской области Белгородской Брянской и
exchange them back to Donetsk,
обменять их потом назад на донецку
Lugansk, that's all. You see, no one
луганску вот и всё выку что никто ничего
will exchange anything, that is, the court will
не будет обменивать то есть суд же
remain in Ukraine, no, the court will remain as it was, So it's
останется в Украине нет суд же как была
Ukraine there
Россия так оста Так она ж Украина там
What flag is
Какой флаг сейчас
hanging now, Russian, no, the Ukrainian flag is there now,
висит российский нет там сейчас флаг
wait, wait, if somewhere
Украина подождите подождите если где-то
on some territory it flies like this
на какой-то территории ходит как это
yellow, like a thieves' flag It means nothing, don't
жёлто блатным флагом Это ни о чём не
look at the court, there is at least one
смотри в суд же есть хоть один
Russian flag on  administration
Российский флаг на администрации
maybe Well I haven't been to court exactly in the
может Ну я в суд же не была именно в
court itself no wait no no ho
самой суд нету не подождите не не хо
heck How many population su and by
хень Сколько население су и по
square meter is not important but this is already
квадратным метра неважно но это уже
territory this is the territory of Ukraine this is
территория это территория Украины это
very important And now let's do this
это очень важно А теперь давайте это
itself people remember yours Well your
само людей пом ваших Ну ваших
Earth wait wait I really
Земля подождите подождите мне очень
Can I come to an agreement I really like
Можно я договорись мне очень нравятся
people who do not live on the territory of
люди которые живут не на территории
Ukraine somewhere there from the
Украины где-то там из
most
самы
patriots so simple Sudzha what
патриоты так просто Суджа это какая
country is this a prophet is also like this this is the most your
страна проро тоже такой это самое ваш
delay gives your country Ukraine
просрочка отдаёт вашу страну Украину
although it is not yours because you live in
хотя она не ваша потому что вы живёте в
Germany I am not from Ukraine at all I am
Германии Я вообще сам не из Украины Я
from Rostov But I live in Germany
сам родом из Ростова Но живу в Германии
Yes I am a citizen of the Russian Federation
Да я гражданин Российской Федерации те
you have already said and I am telling you for the fact that
вы уже говорили а я говорю вам за то что
you are a Patriot you are for Ukraine but you are not
вы Патриот вы за Украину топите но не в
aware that your Zelensky is not mine
курсе о том что ваш Зеленский это не мой
again not mine Zelen I am from Russia I
ещё раз не мой Зелен Я из России ещё раз
repeat once again I am a citizen of Russia from Rost you
повторяю Я гражданин России из Росто вы
Wait the fact that you are from Rostov and live
Подождите то что вы из Ростова и живёте
in Germany does not make you not a
в Германии это не делает вас не
patriot of Ukraine you are a Patriot of Ukraine
патриотом Украины вы Патриот Украины
because you have Well let's say at least the
потому что у вас Ну допустим хотя бы то
same your fork  on the cap this is already this is
же самой ваша вилка на кепке это уже это
already enough No this is this is not a fork this is the
уже достаточно Нет это это это не вилка
grb triu of the great prince Vladimir
это грб триу великого князя Владимира
who baptized
который крестил
ru Let's wait If you want to
ру Давайте Подождите Если вы хотите
Speak And in coins on a coin so take a
Говори А монетах по монета так возьми
horos calmly
горос спокойно
calmly baby baby look extra
спокойно малышка малышка смотри лишний
this is not a reason for aggression Calm down without
это не повод для агрессии Успокойся не
exciting at all
возбуждая вобще
you are not a weight What te di
нере ты веш
75 And how much do you weigh
ди 75 А ты сколько весишь
What ve Well I'm interested in such large
Какая ве Ну мне интересно такие крупные
women for what purpose Maybe I want to
женщины с какой целью Может я хочу к
come to you in the course we'll do something there
тебе в курс приехать там что-то замутим
I'm a zhnin of Russia Come I te A meeting
Я же жнин России Приезжай я те Встречу
along Sudzha we'll walk along Sudzha not
по Судже пройдёмся по Судже не
steal what do you think we'll walk beats with lag
укра что ты думаешь пройдёмся такты с
you with
лагом ты с
lag Give me your phone Come on I'll
лагом Давай свой телефончик Давай я
come Come on in one hand blah the other
приеду Давай в одной руке бла другой
give me the phone I'll come I don't know By the way, what is the
давай телефон я приеду я не знаю Кстати
correct German or don't give the
как правильно германский или не давай
phone what is the correct German or
телефон как правильно немецкий или
Germanic in German Germanic in Russian
германски по немецки германски по-русски
German Here give me the phone Baby I'll
немецки Вот давай телефон Малышка я
come phone I'll give you  I won't give it to you,
приеду телефон я тебе не дам давай свой
write down yours, I remembered it, but you won't remember It
записывай я запомнил да ты не запомнишь
means you don't want to. Come on, write it down, take
Значит ты не хочешь Давай запиши возьми
three. When you arrive, you'll come and
три Ты когда приедешь ты придёшь и
say, I'm right here, somewhere, this is with I'll
скажешь я вот тут вот где-то это с я
find you. And like, here. Show me the most
тебя найду А типа вот Покажите мне самую
skillful thing they are. And this is
искус они таки А это же вот
this, well, let me be for you. Come on, you go. Let's
это ну пусть я буду для тебя Давай ты
move on. Hello, Hello, where are
Поехали дальше Здравствуйте Здравствуйте
you from, St. Petersburg, did you come there
Вы откуда санкт-петербург приехали туда
or were you born there, was
или родились там
born there, I understand. I myself am originally from
родилась ту понял Я сам родом из
Krasnodar. But I've been living in
Краснодара Но живу в
[music]
[музыка]
Germany, Hamburg, for 18 years now. In 2
Германии Гамбурге уже 18 лет через 2
years, BU DTO. Who do you have there, a
года БУ дто Это кто у вас там хвостик
white tail? I see,
белый Я смотрю это
who's the Dalmatian? Pony, like, a very long
кто далматин Поня яко что длинный очень
tail,
хвост
such a cutie, cutie, yes. I
такая милашка милашка да
wonder.
интересно
Three more cats are running around. You have
сост бегает ещё три кота бегают у вас
four cats and two dogs at home. I have two
четыре кота и две собаки дома У меня две
dogs. Three cats, a cat, a snake, a frog, and a
собаки Три кота кошечка змея лягушка и
fish. And a
рыбка а
man. No, no. Pony. Can you snake?
мужчина Нет нету Поня А можете змея
What kind of corn
Какая у вас маисовая
strip do you have? Corn stripes. It's not found in Russia.  we
полос маисовый полосы Он же в России не
buy it well well I mean it's
это покупаем Ну ну это имею в виду
interesting yes and the frog
интересно да а лягушка
What kind of Argentine spurred albino is
Какая аргентинская шпорцевая альбинос
it a white albino yes yes Can you
она альбинос белая да да А можете
show it I wonder you have a pretty
показать Интересно у вас довольно
interesting
интересная
collection no I can't show it
коллекция нет показать не могу потому
because I'll need a new snake can you
что мне надо будет новы полоза можете
bring it Well if you wait I'll wait for the
принести Ну если вы подождёте подожду
snake Yes I wanted to be a serpin tologon when I was a kid
полоза Да я в детстве хотел быть серпин
so I know a lot Okay
тологон так что я знаю очень много Окей
let's wait now
давайте жду сейчас
Wow cool
Вау круто
cool girl 5
прикольно девочка 5
years old class She's so
лет клас Она же
cool And the toad Where do you have it here in
вот прикольно А жаба Где у вас тут она в
Well not on the tattoos on the
Ну в не на татушках на
tattoos It's there
татушках Она
on the back I
там на спине В
mean Well almost Show no but I understand
смысле Ну почти Покажите нет а о понял
Not quite on the back I understand it seems to me
Не совсем на спине я понял мне кажется
the strip wants to stroke your neck No she's
полос хочет погладить вам шее Нет она
generally a boring girl she doesn't
вообще ла скучная девочка она не
accept anyone except
принимает никого единственного кроме
me If someone comes up to her even
меня Если к ней кто-то подойдёт даже
just next to the washing machine he starts
просто рядом стиральном он начинает
hissing she accepts me And she's been with you Since
шипеть меня она принимает А она у вас С
what age And she was 2 months old when I
какого возраста А ей было 2 месяца когда
took her That is, she was still
её забрала То есть она ещё была
small Yes that's it
маленькая Да вот так
cool interesting yes yes And what do you
да прикольно интересно да да А кем
do
работаете
I'm a motorcycle rental instructor  instructor at a
я инструктор мото проката инструктор в
motorcycle school instructor on quad pone on
мотошколе инструктор по квадра поне по
snowmobiles
снегоходам
cool interesting so let's say more so a
прикольно интересно так более скажем так
male sphere there a woman is
мужская сфера там женщина
rare Well, gasoline flows in my veins
редкость Ну в моих жилах течёт бензин
Cool And how let's say other
Прикольно А как скажем другие
instructors are jealous that your gasoline is more
инструктора ревнуют что ваш бензин более
T not with me the boys who work
Т не у меня мальчишки которые работают
with me they are maximally adequate very
со мной они максимально адекватные очень
kind and support me they have a bug there it does
добрые и поддерживает меня у них там баг
not stall because of
не глохнет из-за
you No everything is fine Yes with the exhaust
вас Нет всё нормально Да с выхлопа тоже
everything is also normal
всё норма
Yes thank God Pony clients
Да слава Богу Поня клиентам
like boys
нравится мальчиков
snake and how do you think why Russia
зме а как вот вы считаете почему Россия
attacked
напала на
Ukraine Oh, how quickly we changed our shoes
Украину Ох как мы быстро переобулись
firstly no one
во-первых никто ни на кого не
attacked anyone And secondly
нападал А во-вторых
secondly why did we change our shoes so quickly
во-вторых с че мы так быстро переобулись
Valya Well I The thing is that today is
Вале Ну я Дело в том что сегодня День
Valentine's Day Yes I went to the summer house with beautiful
Валентина Да я зашёл в летку с красивыми
girls what February with beautiful girls
девушко че февраля с красивыми девушками
to talk about love romance yes let's
поговорить о любви романтике да
start with the fact that today is February 14th
начнём с того то что сегодня 14 февраля
I'm telling you today I'm talking with beautiful
Я же говорю я сегодня с красивыми
girls about love and romance Yes
девушками общаюсь о любви и романтике Да
great yes  Why do you think
прекрасно да Как вы считаете почему
Putin attacked Ukraine? No one
Путин напал на Украину никто ни на кого
attacked anyone. Why did he lead troops into
не нападал Ну почему он вёл войска в
Ukraine? No one brought anyone in. Well,
Украину Никто никого не вводил ну
Russian troops entered
российские войска зашли на территорию
Ukrainian territory. I understand correctly.
Украины я правильно понимаю
Not
Не
Russian. People entered. They did
российские Люди зашли
n't even
даже не
enter. But they came to
зашли А пришли
liberate
освободить
people. From where? From where? What kind of people? From
людей откуда От чего откуда Каких людей
what city? People. Liberate.
с какого города людей Освободи От чего
From what? Let's tell us. From what? From what trend?
давайте от чего А расскажите от чего от
From what trend? Which trend
трендец так От трендец от какого трен
was going on in Ukraine? Which trend is it? Which trend is it? Which trend is it? Let's do it right now.
деца который творился в Украине какой
Look, you have the coat of arms of Ukraine.
Вы же смотрите у вас герб Украины
Let's do it right away.
давайте так сразу Смотри
Look. I am a citizen of the Russian Federation. Look again. I am Saro from Rostov. I live in
раз смотрите я Саро из Ростова Я живу в
Germany. I heard. I heard you. I heard you.
Германии услышала я услышала вас я
Please.
услышала отне пожалуйста
Of course, you have a
му конечно то у вас есть
man. No, but I have a man in my house. Maybe you
мужик нет но у меня в доме есть му може
can give him headphones for a minute. I
можешь ему дать на минутку наушники Я
want to ask him. No, please. Are you
хочу спросить у него нет нет пожа ты
afraid? You know
боишься знаете почему
why? And he has
почему А он у тебя
no
сшк нет
military personnel. Give him headphones. Let him not
военный дай ему наушники Пусть он не
show himself in front of the camera. Just give him headphones.
показывается в кадр просто Наушники вот
Why? Because I am talking to you.
дай Почему Потому что я с вами
with you started a dialogue he is
разговариваю с вами диалог начали он
you bug or is it just like that
тебе баг заправляет или это просто так
Friend oh-oh-oh oh-oh-oh it's a friend friend
Друг ой-ой-ой ой-ой-ой это друг друг
Got it yes So tell me from whom did you come to
Понял да Так расскажи от кого пришли
free Your
освобождать Ваши
guys from your rules from no one Father And
ребята от ваших правил ни от кого Отче А
what are the rules What rules were
какие там правила Какие правила были
very not very good Which specifically not very
очень не очень хорошие Какие конкретно
good Well so specifically Voice What are
не очень хорошие Ну так конкретно Озвучь
these rules not very good So
Какие эти правила не очень хорошие Так
you know If you have a coat of arms on your
вы же знаете Если вы у вас герб и на
head and on your chest
голове и на груди
children Calm down please and even On a
дети Успокойтесь пожалуйста и даже На
beautiful cat I hope your
котике прекрасном Я надеюсь это ваша
daughter knitted it He is so
дочь связала Он такой
cool what were the rules in
классный то какие там правила были в
Ukraine that we attacked who the cat
Украине что мы напали кого кто котика
is a badger and not a cat and this is a badger Okay
это барсук а не кот а это барсук Да окей
who is it I don't know my friends from Ukraine
кто его Я не знаю мне друзья из Украины
sent it to me Oh how lovely well then
прислали Ай какая прелесть ну то
Explain From what rules did the Russians come to save
Объясните От каких правил пришли спасать
people in Ukraine Let's go So I will
россияне людей в Украине Давайте Так я
not communicate with you on a political topic
на политическую тему общаться с вами не
but support your what you are
буду а поддерживать ваше то что вы
now trying to lead me somewhere
сейчас пытаетесь меня вывести куда-то
incomprehensible conversation to negativity and that's all
непонятный разговор на негатив и всё вот
I will not on this topic we either
на вот эту вот тему я не буду мы либо
communicate normally
общаемся нормально
on other topics Or we say goodbye to you
на другие темы Либо мы с вами прощаемся
on  others are what Well,
на другие это
we talked about
какие Ну вот мы с вами общались на по
animals for example here Let's talk
поводу животных например вот Давайте по
about animals the topic of animals I'm
поводу животных тема животных Меня
interested in why the Russians came to
интересует почему российские пришли в
Ukraine Okay, we'll say goodbye I
Украину Ладно мы с вами попрощаемся я
wish you all the best And you go
вам желаю всего хорошего А вы идите
Put a like Who wants this let's go
Ставьте лайк Кто хочет этого поехали
write to Telegram right now axis VN and
пись на й Telegram прям зараз ось ВН а
pok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through SRG OR in your ban and very
нас через срг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos are not shown to people at times
багато вдео не показуе людям вчасно не
information about streams is not shown so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational links are
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
written right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
Telegram will okrim video also interesting and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we are obliged to you to
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
keep constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
letter a
пись а